** SEE THE ASSIGNMENT BRIEF **

https://stackoverflow.com/questions/30097648/difference-between-a-direct-mapped-cache-and-fully-associative-cache

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NupfchrINeA

https://stackoverflow.com/questions/29808525/java-cache-simulation-with-lru-gives-an-inaccurate-hit-rate

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cache_replacement_policies

/** code notes **/

 The cache is described by four integers:

    W is the number of bits in one word. This number will be a multiple of 8.
    C is the number of data bytes in the cache. This number will be a power of 2. (In C, we do not count the space needed to store tags, just the space needed to store data.)
    B is the number of bytes in one cache block. This number will be a divisor of C.
    k is the number of lines in a block. This number will be a divisor of B. 

/**
*	W is the bits in an address
*	C is bytes in the cache
*	1 block has B bytes
*	k lines in 1 block
*/

All W, C, B and k will be positive integers. The number W of bits in a word will be ≤1024
. The size C of the cache will not exceed the number of available addresses: C≤2W. The number kC/B of lines in the cache will be ≤220

.

Each memory access is described by one address, which is a W-bit integer, in the interval [0,2W)
. Such an address is the index in memory of the byte being accessed. The number of memory accesses will be ≤220. 

For each memory access in the input, print 'C' if it is served by the cache, and print 'M' if it is served by the memory. Whitespace (space and newlines) will be ignored, so use it as you see fit. 

1. take a file name File file = new File()....
2. Scanner
3. read first line
4. do checks
5. doSomething()
6. read everything else as appropriate
7. doSomethingElse()
8. get the output string

@END write to filename.out

/********
https://stackoverflow.com/questions/18685765/are-the-predefined-java-linkedlists-doubly-linked
https://stackoverflow.com/questions/22675930/moving-head-of-linked-list-to-tail
Convert memory address to binary, split into tag, index and offset
search doublylinkedlist, if found - move to right most position (PRINT C) else add to doublylinkedlist remove left item (PRINT M), 